《反恐24小时》前情回顾
我是埃克·杜巴库上校
This is Colonel Ike Dubaku.
我们拥有CIP装置
We have the CIP device.
明日此时
We demand the complete withdrawal
美国的海军
of the U.S. Naval Strike Force
必须全部撤退
by this time tomorrow.
你要撤兵
You are recalling the invasion force.
此事尚需考虑
Well, that determination has yet to be made.
我请求你
I implore you
别放弃我的国家
do not abandon my country.
是萨曼莎·罗斯
It's Samantha Roth.
她说她要告诉我
She says, she has new information
犬子之死的新消息
regarding my son's death.
罗杰被安排审计部门内部的经纪人
Roger was tasked with auditing the brokers in his department.
他发现了其他的地下账户
He uncovered other blind accounts
根据这些账户我们追查到
accounts that were traced to a senior member
你妻子的一位高级官员
of your wife's administration.
你要的都在这里
It's all here.
银行账号  交易记录
Account numbers, trading records
他所知的一切
everything that he knew.
肯定是鲍尔和阿尔梅达的手下
Bauer must have worked out this escape
一起策划了逃跑
with Almeida's people.
我被这混蛋给耍了
That son of a bitch played me.
他骗我说局里已遭渗透
Had me believing the Bureau was compromised--
有人在内部搞鬼
someone on the inside working against us.
现如今我才知道都是他搞的鬼
I realize now it was him all along.
我们俩都被耍了
He played us both.
我要挽回这个错误  拉里
I'm going to make this right, Larry.
我要不惜代价找到鲍尔和阿尔梅达
Whatever it takes, I will find Bauer and Almeida.
你时间不多了  坦纳  把你知道的都说出来
You're out of time, Mr. Tanner. Tell me what you know.
我半个字都不会说
I'm not going to tell you a damn thing.
阿尔梅达在哪里
Where is Almeida?
坦纳说阿尔梅达那伙人计划绑架
Tanner says Almeida's crew has a plan to abduct
桑加拉前总理
former Prime Minister of Sangala.
马托波
Matobo?
-什么时候  -差不多是现在
- When? - Pretty much now.
你为什么不让当局来处理
Why didn't you call the authorities?
-他不能  杰克  -为什么
- He couldn't, Jack. - Why not?
他发现爱默生的客户正是杜巴库
He found out Emerson's client was Dubaku.
你认为他在政府里安插了间谍
That's who you believe has agents inside the government.
杜巴库是整件事的关键
Dubaku is the key to this thing, Jack.
要想揭露这个阴谋
If we're going to uncover the conspiracy
我们必须在他离开美国前找到他
we have to get to him before he leaves the U.S.
-我从联调局逃了出来  -听说了
- I got away from the FBI. - Yeah, I heard.
我还听说是杰克·鲍尔帮你逃脱的
I also heard it was Jack Bauer who broke you out.
他是我们的人了
He's on board now.
"货"是一个人
The package is a person.
桑加拉前总理  马托波
Former Prime Minister Matobo of Sangala.
任务就是抓住他  并移交给杜巴库上校
The assignment is to grab him, deliver him to Colonel Dubaku.
马托波在哪里  他在哪里
Where's Matobo?! Where is he?!
这是藏身处  钢筋混凝土结构
It's a safe room; reinforced concrete.
杰克  如果我们空手而归
Jack, we leave here without Matobo
就会失去抓住杜巴库的唯一机会
we lose our only chance of getting at Dubaku.
以下事件发生于下午12点至1点之间
马托波的警卫长说
Matobo's security chief
他住处有一个藏身处
said there's a safe room at his residence.
他们夫妇应该已经进入躲避
They should have him and his wife locked down by now.
他们不会有事
They'll be safe till your team gets there.
抓阿尔梅达是要务  把他带回来
Your priority is to grab Almeida and bring him back here.
我们会尽量使用非致命武器
We'll make every effort to use nonlethal force
但阿尔梅达那伙人都是军人出身
but Almeida's crew is ex-military.
要制服他们不太容易
They're going to be hard to subdue
除非我的人可以回击
unless my men can return fire.
你的人将置身险境  我理解
I understand you'll be exposing your men
-但是你必须冒这个险  -长官
- but it's a risk you need to take. - Sir...
阿尔梅达是目前唯一能帮我们
Almeida is the only viable lead we've got
取回CIP装置的人
to retrieve the CIP device.
一定要留活口  明白吗
You need to bring him in alive, is that understood?
明白
Understood.
行动
Let's move out.
上车后会得到最新情况
We'll get our updates in the van.
打开藏身处大门
Open the safe room.
我会打到你开门为止
I will keep going until you open the door.
我说过
I've already told you.
门一旦关闭  就只能从里面打开
Once it's closed, you can only open it from the inside.
随你怎样处置我
Do whatever you want to me
但你永远都进不去
but you will never get into that room.
我们必须抓到马托波
We've got to get Matobo.
抓不到他  我们将一无所获
Without him, we've got nothing.
我知道
I know.
-想到办法进去了吗  -没有
- Find a way in yet? - No.
利特法克  有办法重接内部通话线路吗
Litvak, any luck reconnecting the intercom?
还没
Not yet.
正在试
I'm working on it.
长官  刚才收到
Sir, this just came in...
我正在指挥外勤行动  艾丽卡
I'm in the middle of a field op, Erika.
现在没空
I don't really have a lot of time right now.
司法部长发过来的
It's from the attorney general.
我觉得你该抽空看看
I think you should make time for this.
-什么东西  -坦纳的律师正准备
- What is it? - Tanner's lawyers are filing a complaint
投诉联调局
against the Bureau.
沃克
Walker.
蕾妮  是我
Renee, it's me.
十五分钟内我会抵达马托波家
I'm less than 15 minutes away from Matobo's house.
到达后我会给战术小组侦查
When I get there, I'll recon for the Tac Team.
-等下  -怎么
- Stop a second. - What?
你是如何得知
This information about Matobo being abducted...
马托波正遭绑一事
tell me how you got it
你应该知道啊  审问坦纳得来的
You know how I got it--I questioned Tanner.
-你审问他了  -对
- You questioned him? - Yeah.
坦纳的律师说
Tanner's lawyers are saying
你把他们锁在医院病房外
you locked them out of his hospital room,
切断了他的呼吸机
then cut off his ventilator.
他们还说你向他的伤口施压
They said you applied pressure to his gunshot wound
我们得找到阿尔梅达
We needed Almeida's location
坦纳不配合
Tanner was not about to cooperate
所以你就严刑逼供
So you tortured him.
你脑子进水了吗
What the hell were you thinking?
我拿到了所需情报
I got the information we needed.
情报真假尚不明了
Information that may not even be valid.
你我心知肚明
You know as well as I do,
严刑逼供不可靠
Coercive interrogation is unreliable.
-不  坦纳没说谎  -你怎么知道
- No, Tanner was not lying.  - You know that?
他不是顺水推舟骗你的
how do you know he wasn't just telling you what you wanted to hear?
等到了马托波那  就清楚了
I'll find out when I get to Matobo's house.
不行  不准你去那
No, you're not going to Matobo's.
你马上给我回办公室来
You're coming back here to the office.
司法部长派人来
The attorney general is sending somebody here,
你要跟他汇报发生的一切
and you're going to tell him everything that happened.
拉里
Larry...
鲍尔跟阿尔梅达跑掉是我的错
it's my fault that Bauer and Almeida are still at large.
求你了  让我了解此事
Please, let me play this out.
找到CIP装置后
I will deal with the consequences
一切责任我来承担
after we find the CIP device.
不行  外勤组已经出发  他们处理就行了
No, the field team is on the way, they can handle this.
蕾妮
Renee,
马上给我回来
get back here now.
对不起  拉里
I'm sorry, Larry,
我必须弥补过错
but I need to make this right.
蕾妮
Renee?
该死的
Damn it.
你没事太好了  宝贝
I'm glad you're all right, babe.
机务人员说
The flight attendant said something about us getting
我们得到优先降落权
a priority clearance to land.
你真幸运
Uh, you got lucky.
是吗
Did I?
咱俩通话后  飞机就获得了优先降落权
I mean, it happened just after we spoke,
我总感觉  这件事跟你有关
so I thought maybe you had something to do with it.
我吗  我怎么可能做得到
Me? How could I have done anything?
听我说  我今天回家会晚些
Listen, I might be late tonight.
这有好多工作要做
There's a lot going on at work.
我都一个星期没见到你了
I haven't seen you in a week.
咱们也应该在一起
I thought we could spend some time together.
吃个晚餐  或者
Dinner, and maybe...
那个一下
...you know.
对不起  我得挂了  工作繁忙
Sorry, I have to go. I have to get back to work.
再打给我
Call me later.
好的
Okay.
外勤组布置妥当了吗
Did you deploy the field teams?
是的  他们刚出发
Yeah, they just left.
我们得跟马托波的警卫长协调
We need to coordinate with Matobo's security chief
再打电话给他
get him back on the line.
这些人为杜巴库卖命  是不是
These people, they work for Dubaku, don't they?
有可能
Possibly.
是的  或许是
Yes, probably.
但如果他们想杀我  我早已经死了
But if they wanted me dead,I would be dead.
那他们想干吗
Then what do they want?
名单
Names.
Names?
桑加拉内部  与我同盟者的名单
Of my allies inside Sangala.
你宁死也不会说的  他们很清楚
You would die before you exposed them, they know that.
是的  他们知道  但是
Yes, they do, but..
问题在我这
Then it's me.
问题出在我这
It's me.
他们打算以我为要挟  逼你说出来
They want to use me to get you to talk?
别担心
Don't worry.
我们在这里很安全  他们走了就好了
We'll be safe in here until they leave.
乌勒  我害怕
Ule, I'm scared.
阿拉玛  听我说
Alama, listen to me.
我们得冷静
We need to stay calm.
我们会平安无事的
We'll be fine.
联调局知道我们被困于此
The FBI knows we are here.
他们会火速前来营救我们
They'll come for us soon.
别担心
Okay?
马托波先生
Mr. Matobo?
我知道您能听见  也能看见我
I know you can see and hear me.
出来吧  不必有人受伤
Come out now and nobody has to get hurt.
别浪费时间了
You are wasting your time.
快出来  不然我会杀了你的手下
Come out now or I will kill your man.
给你一分钟时间
You have one minute.
50秒
Fifty...
我愿为您捐躯  长官
I am prepared to die, sir.
为了您  为了桑加拉
For you and for Sangala.
埃托奥说得对
Eto'o is right.
没有了你  桑加拉就失去了领袖
Without you,Sangala has no leader.
人民需要你
The people need you.
还剩30秒
30 seconds.
埃托奥是不会被你吓倒的
Eto'o's courage is stronger than your threats.
他已准备牺牲
He is willing to die.
对他所做的牺牲  我将永世感怀
And for that sacrifice he has my eternal gratitude,
桑加拉的人民也会永远感激他
and the gratitude of the people of Sangala.
还剩10秒
Ten seconds.
时间到
Time's up.
15分钟前我还跟他通过话呢
I just got through to him 15 minutes ago.
但是他现在没接
Well, he's not answering now.
那就再打给住所的其他人
Then get me someone else at the residence.
是联调局
It's the FBI.
联调局知道我们在这
Does the FBI know we're here?
是坦纳告密了
Tanner.
只有他知道我们的计划
He's the only one who knew we were grabbing Matobo.
他肯定是招了
He must have talked.
长官  我们得在他们到达之前离开
Sir, we need to go before they get here.
不能留下马托波
Not without Matobo.
这些墙有两英尺厚
Those walls are two feet thick.
就算用聚能弹炸开一个洞
Even if we blow a hole with a shaped charge
里面的人也活不了
they'll kill everyone inside.
我找到办法了
I think I found a way.
是吗  什么
Yeah? Like what?
我们用毒气把他们逼出来
We can gas them out.
-我们没有毒气  -那就想办法弄来
- We don't have anything! - We'll find something!
有一个通风系统
There's a ventilation system
直通藏身处
running straight into the safe room.
如果能通气进去  就能把他们逼出来
If I can feed the gas through that, it'll flush 'em out.
联调局马上就来了
The FBI is coming!
他们15分钟之内到不了
They won't be here for at least 15 minutes.
你在说什么  你怎么知道
What are you talking about? How do you know?
若他们在我们到达之前就知道了
If they knew anything before we got here
他们会立刻转移马托波
they'd have evacuated Matobo.
那只是猜测
That's just guesswork.
战术小组已不在特区内
The tac teams are staged out of the DC branch office
他们离这有21里
That's 21 miles from here, with traffic.
我们至少有15分钟
That gives us at least 15 minutes.
我们不能留下马托波
We're not leaving without Matobo.
杜巴库雇我们就是为了这个
That's what Dubaku is paying us for.
-你该不会是真打算  -闭嘴
- You're not seriously considering... - Shut up!
你说的是哪种气体
What kind of gas are you talking about?
双硬脂铵
Ammonium dysterate.
从普通日用品中就能制备出来
We can make it from basic household products.
-就这么办  -托尼  帮我一把
- Do it. - Tony, give me a hand.
杰克  你知道如果用双硬脂铵
Jack, you do know ammonium dysterate could kill them
他们很可能在被逼出来之前就会死
as easily as flush them out.
我们必须赌一把
That's a chance we're gonna have to take.
运送马托波是我们唯一
Delivering Matobo is our only chance
接近杜巴库和CIP装置的机会
to get to Dubaku and the CIP device.
行了  拿上这些碗
I got it. Grab those bowls.
进入通风口了吗
Gotten into the vent yet?
是
Yeah!
联调局马上就到了
The FBI will be here any minute.
马托波先生
Mr. Matobo...
我们已控制藏身处的通风口
we've accessed the air intake to your safe room.
现在正释放双硬脂铵气体
We are now feeding in ammonium dysterate gas.
若不开门  你将必死无疑
If you do not open the door you will die.
我相信你愿意牺牲自己的生命
I believe that you are willing to sacrifice your life.
但是您愿意
But are you also willing
让您的妻子也因你而死吗
to sentence your wife to death?
乌勒
Ule...
你知道开门的后果
You know what they will do if we open the door.
我知道
I know.
我不能让他们逼我说出那些名字
I can't let them force me to name names.
国家的事业比我们重要的多
Our cause is more important than we are.
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
-詹尼斯·古德  -是我
- Janis Gold? - Yes?
我是雷蒙德·哈维尔
I'm Raymond Howell
来自司法部长办公室
from the Attorney General's office
我们到哪里谈谈
Is there some place we can talk?
-谈什么  -医院的事  古德小姐
- About?  - What happened at the hospital, Ms. Gold.
沃克探员被指控
Agent Walker's being accused
虐待嫌疑人
of torturing your suspect.
他不是我的嫌疑人  我不知道
He's not my suspect, I have no idea what happened
我离开房间之后发生了什么  跟我无关
after I left that room, I am not involved.
嫌疑人的律师称  你把他们
The suspect's attorneys claim that you sent them
引去了错误的病房
to the wrong hospital room
来给沃克探员争取更多时间
to buy Agent Walker more time.
在我看来  这跟你有关
So it sounds to me like you were involved.
你得等等
This is going to have to wait.
-詹尼斯  我需要你设置通信  -莫斯探员
Janis, I need you on comm, now. Agent Moss
-司法部长亲自对此立案调查  -哈维尔
- the A.G. personally initiated this investigation. - Howell
你自己看看  我们有紧急情况
open your eyes, we have a situation.
她现在不能处理此事
She cannot deal with this right now.
拜托
Please
坐一下  过来
have a seat. Come here.
怎么了
What's going on?
估计阿尔梅达一伙已到达马托波住所
We think Almeida and his crew may already at Matobo's.
我们联系不上蕾妮  无法通知她
And we can't reach Renee to warn her.
-为何联系不上  -我听说她的所作所为
- Why can't you reach her?  - When I heard what she did
我命令她回总部来
to Tanner, I ordered her back to headquarters
向司法部长办公室报告
to talk to the A.G's office
她拒绝了  还关掉了手机
and she, uh, refused, turned off her cell.
我要你布置特警组布点
I need you running point on SWAT.
好的  谢谢
Okay, thanks.
希林格  继续联络蕾妮
Hillinger, keep trying to reach Renee.
我们时间不多了
We're running out of time.
放更多的毒气进去
Put more gas in!
那样他们会马上送命的
If we do, it'll kill them instantly.
杰克  还要多久
How much time is it going to take, Jack?
这要看他们
It's up to them.
我没法呼吸
I can't breathe.
闭上眼睛  从容以对
Just close your eyes, let it happen.
如果打开门  后果更是不堪设想
I know if we open that door, it will be worse.
我爱你
I love you.
阿拉玛  不要
Alama, no!
快把他带出来
Get him out of there!
这女人也带走
Get the woman, too.
深呼吸  你不会有事的
Just breathe, you'll be all right.
呼吸
Just breathe.
好了  快撤
Okay, let's go!
我对不起你
I'm so sorry.
快点
Come on.
我是莫斯
It's Moss.
拉里  我是蕾妮
Larry, it's Renee.
蕾妮  听着
Renee, listen.
鲍尔和阿尔梅达可能已在马托波住处
Bauer and Almeida may already be at Matobo's.
的确  我看到他们
They are, I've got a visual on them
正把马托波夫妇装上卡车
loading Matobo and his wife into a truck.
-特警组跑哪里去了  -还有多久
- Where the hell is SWAT? - How long for SWAT?
还差五分钟
They're still about five minutes out.
蕾妮  退后
Renee, listen to me, I want you
等待特警组支援
to stand down and fallback until they get there.
你听到了吗
Do you hear me?
让我搞清楚车牌号
Let me just get a plate on the vehicle.
把枪放下
Drop the gun.
蕾妮
Renee?
该死
Damn it!
詹尼斯  再联系她
Janis, try getting her back.
哪支特警队会先到现场
Whose SWAT team will be first on scene?
里梅克队
Remick's.
我要和他通话  快
Get him for me, now.
给我走开
Move!
爱默生先生
Mr. Emerson!
就我观察  她是一个人
Far as I can tell, she's alone.
该死的鲍尔  你个狗娘养的
Damn you, Bauer, you son of a bitch.
她是联调局的人
She's FBI.
她叫沃克  是她把我从参议院听证会里
Her name is Walker. She's the one that pulled me
弄出来寻找托尼
out of the Senate hearing to help find Tony.
别干傻事
Don't be stupid.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
坦纳对你的计划了解多少
How much does Tanner know about your operation?
足够多了
Enough to cause problems.
我们要从她那里搞清楚
We need to find out from her what he
他对联调局说了多少  在此之前
told the FBI--  till then
-先留她活口  -大卫  他说得对
- we do nothing.  - He's right, David.
我们要弄清有没有其他消息泄露出去
We need to be sure nothing else has been compromised.
把她带上车
Get her in the cage.
别碰我
Don't you touch me.
-把你的手拿开  -闭嘴  不然
- Get your hands off of me!  - Shut up or I will
有你好看
shut you up.
她身上没武器
She's clean.
我们走
Let's go!
-抓到马托波了  -没错
- Do you have Matobo?  - Yeah.
还有他老婆  但我们
And the wife, but we ran
出了些岔子
into a complication.
什么岔子
A complication?
联调局已经知道了这次行动
FBI knew about the operation.
说明坦纳已经泄密了
Which means Tanner talked.
-这不是什么好消息  -我也不希望这样
- I don't like this. - No, neither do I.
我们抓到了他们的一个探员
We got one of their agents
她叫沃克
with us, her name's Walker.
联络你在
I need you to check
局里的眼线
with your source at the Bureau,
看她知道多少
find out how much she knows.
-好的  -如果你的内线没查出什么
- All right. - If your source doesn't come up
我们到了以后再拷问她
with anything, we'll interrogate her when we get there.
我居然相信了你
Can't believe I trusted you.
你这个婊子养的骗子
You lying son of a bitch.
老哥  事关重大
This is important, man.
对他  对我都很重要
To him and me.
多谢  感激不尽
Thanks, appreciate it.
有何进展
Any luck?
有  先生
Yes, sir.
我很抱歉花了这么久
I'm sorry it took so long,
我有个朋友给在私人企业
but I tracked down a friend who does crypto
做解密业务  他说他可以
for the private sector-- he says he should
把U盘上的文件解密
be able to crack the files  on the thumb-drive.
只要不是军用或以上级别的加密手段
Provided the, uh, encryption isn't military grade or better.
我认为罗杰接触不到这些
I doubt Roger would have had access to anything like that.
他还说如果你找国安局帮忙
He also said you'd have a lot easier job
事情就容易多了
if you just went to the NSA.
我们得先搞清楚
Not until we know
我太太的内阁中有多少人已被收买
how badly my wife's administration's been compromised.
我朋友说20分钟后在他家见面
My friend said he'd meet us at his apartment in 20 minutes.
他能信得过吗
Do you trust him?
是的
Yes
萨曼莎说这些文件能证明
Samantha says the documents would prove
我儿子是被谋杀的
my son was murdered.
我会告诉他此事不可外泄
I'll make sure he understands this can't go anywhere.
谢谢你  布莱恩
Thank you, Brian.
你不了解我这些日子的感受
You don't know what it's been like.
一直以来  从骨子里  我就深信
All this time knowing in my bones
罗杰是不会自杀的
Roger didn't commit suicide
人们一直忍受着我这种想法
and having people just tolerate me
告诉我  我只是伤心才那么说
tell me it was my grief talking.
我一定要找到杀我儿子的凶手  布莱恩
I'm going to find the people who did this to my son Brian.
我要让他们血债血偿
And I am going to make them pay.
长官  请恕我多嘴
Sir if I may...
说吧
What is it?
你至少应该知会总统阁下
Shouldn't you at least tell the President
告诉她你的打算
what you're doing?
现在不能告诉她
I can't take this to my wife...
我得先确认此事不假
until I can prove it.
您要见我
You wanted to see me?
有件事我晓得
One thing I've learned:
总统交不到新朋友
presidents don't make new friends.
所以有事情他们会找老朋友
That's why they lean on their old ones.
我需要你的支持  伊桑
I'll need your support Ethan.
我要下令
I'm going to authorize
依计划开始对桑加拉的军事行动
the military operation in Sangala as planned.
总统阁下
Madame President...
你无需提醒我后果  伊桑
You don't need to list the consequences, Ethan.
我在西非做的任何行动
Any action I take in West Africa
都可能导致我们遭受恐怖袭击
will likely result in a terrorist attack here
但我若不采取行动  全桑加拉的人民
but if I take no action, an entire generation
将会被屠杀殆尽
of Sangalans will be wiped out.
舆论会指责
Your critics will point out
您宣誓保护本国人民
you took an oath to protect the people of  this  country.
正是为了达到这个目的
And the way to do that
我才不会向勒索与恐吓屈服
is not give in to blackmail and threats.
伊桑
Ethan...
抵抗桑加拉的屠杀暴政
taking a stand against the genocide in Sangala
已经使我们在世界上
has reestablished our leadership and our moral authority
重塑了领袖地位和道德权威
in the eyes of the world.
我不能  也不会退缩的
I cannot and I will not back down.
说
Yes?
总统阁下  国务卿史蒂文斯
Madame President, Secretary of State Stevens
前来找您
is here to see you.
-有要事相商  -叫他进来
- It's urgent. - Send him in.
出什么事情了  乔
What is it Joe?
联调局刚汇报说
The FBI just reported
总理马托波及其夫人
that Prime Minister Matobo and his wife
在他们的住处被绑架了
were abducted from their residence.
什么
What?!
被谁绑架的
Abducted by whom?
保镖辨认出了杰克·鲍尔和托尼·阿尔梅达
His bodyguards identified Jack Bauer and Tony Almeida
他们两人参与其中
as two of the men involved
杜巴库已同时拥有CIP装置和马托波
which means Dubaku has the CIP device and Matobo.
联调局的搜寻结果如何
Where is the FBI on finding him?
有线索么
Do they have any active leads?
还没有  总统阁下
Not yet Madame President.
他们刚开始搜寻工作
They're just beginning the search operation.
咱们得谈谈
I think we need to talk
马托波遭绑架对进军的影响
about how Matobo's abduction affects the invasion.
在进军之后  只有马托波有着广泛支持
Matobo is the only man with enough popular support
和实力去领导桑加拉
and strength to lead Sangala after an invasion.
没有他  国家将四分五裂
Without him,the country would collapse
陷入混乱之中
in complete bloodshed and chaos.
因此  如今的上策
Which means the best course of action may be
或是是满足杜巴库的要求  撤兵
to meet Dubaku's demand and withdraw our forces.
上策
The best course of action
是找到杜巴库和绑架他的人
is to find Matobo and the people who took him.
让联调局与各相关机构协调合作
And make sure the FBI brings in every relevant agency.
是的  阁下
Yes ma'am.
那么  关于进军
So... where do we stand with your decision
您到底想如何决定
to go through with the invasion?
离杜巴库的时限还有30分钟
We still have 30 minutes before Dubaku's deadline.
在此之前必须找到马托波
I want Matobo found by then.
我刚发给了你新搜查坐标
I just sent you new search coordinates.
请给外勤组上更新坐标
Upload a grid to the ground teams please.
我已经做了  他们正调整搜寻范围
I already did; they're adjusting their perimeter now.
好的  谢谢
All right thanks.
听着  艾丽卡
Listen Erika.
怎么
What?
先前我发神经  很抱歉
I'm sorry I was a jerk before.
你只是担心你的妻子
You're worried about your wife on a plane.
没事的
It's cool.
她已经在地面上了
She's on the ground now.
她的飞机降落了  幸运之极
Her plane landed; she got lucky.
那太好了
That's great news.
她没事我真高兴
I'm glad she's okay.
西恩
Hey Sean.
昨晚的事  我一直不能释怀
I can't stop thinking about last night.
我也是
Yeah me, too.
打扰
Excuse me.
西恩  我需要你帮我照看下电脑
Sean, I need you to babysit the downloads on my computer.
我正下载鉴证组从马托波住处
They're coming in from the forensics team
传来的数据
at Matobo's residence.
现在就去
Now please.
好的  当然
Okay sure.
打扰了
Excuse me.
雷米克的小组刚完成
Remick's team just finished
对马托波住址的地毯式搜查
a sweep of the Matobo residence.
你要想跟他通话  他在2号线
He's on line two if you want to talk to him.
等等  詹尼斯
Janis wait.
找到蕾妮了吗
Did you find Renee?
没有  长官
No, sir.
马托波的保镖
But one of Matobo's bodyguards
看见她被鲍尔和阿尔梅达带走
saw her being taken by Bauer and Almeida.
那她还活着
Then she's alive.
她和马托波在一起
She's with the Matobos.
追踪她的手机
We'll run a trace on her cell.
无法追踪  长官
Can't do that, sir.
现场发现沃克探员的手机和武器
We recovered Agent Walker's phone and weapon on-site.
鉴证组正在检查现场
Forensics is still sweeping the scene.
等有了结果
All right, I want to be the first to know
-第一个告诉我  -好的
if they find something. Yes, sir.
好吧
All right, um...
将蕾妮的照片和体貌特征发到各处
get Renee's picture and description out to all agencies.
随时向我更新
Put me in the queue
国土安全局的最新进展
for a real-time update from Homeland.
好的
Okay.
詹尼斯
Janis.
让本办公室的每个人
I want everybody in this office
都以找到她为首要任务
to make finding her their top priority.
明白吗
Is that understood?
明白
It is.
你还好吗
Are you going to be okay?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
回去工作
Just get to work.
对不起  我没有保护好您  阁下
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you, sir.
不需要道歉
You have nothing to apologize for.
杰克  他们给了你多少钱
How much are they paying you, Jack?
我希望
I hope it's enough
当他们拿CIP装置杀死无辜的美国人后
to live with yourself when they kill innocent Americans
这钱够你用
with the CIP device.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你的所作所为将令多少人死去
How many people will die because of what you're doing?
爱默生
Emerson.
你说对了
You were right.
沃克探员让坦纳招了
Agent Walker broke Tanner.
坦纳说了多少
How much did Tanner spill?
只说了绑架马托波的细节
Other than the details of Matobo's abduction, nothing.
-你确定吗  -确定
- You're sure? - Positive.
沃克无足轻重
Walker is extraneous.
来之前干掉她
Kill her before you get here.
好的  我们马上到
Okay, we'll be with you soon.
快点
Be quick about it.
杜巴库急于见到总理
Dubaku's anxious to get his hands on the prime minister.
尼科尔斯问过联调局的内线
Nichols checked with his source at the Bureau.
沃克不知道任何
Walker doesn't know anything
有关行动的消息
that can compromise the operation.
你相信尼科尔斯的内线吗
You trust Nichols' source?
他相信
Nichols does.
这就够了
That's good enough for me.
利特法克  计划改变
Litvak, change of plan.
莫里森大街口右转
Take a right on Morrison Avenue.
莫里森那有什么
What's on Morrison?
废弃的工地  我们把她抛尸于此
Abandoned construction site-- we'll dump her there.
安全起见  应该先弄清楚她知道多少
Shouldn't we find out for ourselves what she knows?
尼科尔斯要我们先除掉她
Nichols wants her out of the way
再送马托波去
before we deliver Matobo.
我理解你们的已全力部署
I understand your deployment's stretched thin
但我们一名探员失踪了
but one of our own agents is missing.
这也很重要
That's a priority, too.
听着  我不管你去哪找人手
Look, look, I don't care where you find the men.
马上派他们出去搜寻
Just get them out there looking.
从未见过他这样
I've never seen him like that.
好像火烧眉毛了
He looks like his head's going to explode.
谢谢
Thank you.
我倒不惊讶
Well, I'm not surprised.
什么意思
Meaning?
很明显  他很在乎蕾妮
Meaning it's fairly obvious he has feelings for Renee.
为什么会这样想
Why do you think that?
直觉  我就知道
Instinct-- I just know.
回岗位上去
Stay on task.
朱玛将军说  美军航母
General Juma says the American carrier troop
尚未开始撤军
still has not begun to withdraw.
他们也没有发动进攻
Well, they haven't launched their invasion either.
我给总统的最后期限  马上就要到了
I gave this president a deadline and it's almost past.
很显然  我们的警告不够分量
Apparently, our demonstration was not convincing enough.
这女人比我们想象的还要固执
This woman is more stubborn than we expected.
一旦她发现我们抓住了马托波
Once she realizes we have Matobo,
她就会改变主意
she'll change her mind.
万一没有呢
And if she doesn't?
你有CIP模块
You have the CIP module.
再发动一次攻击
Launch another attack.
当美国人民开始死亡
Let's see how stubborn she is after American civilians
看她还能多固执
start dying.
马托波什么时候到
When will Matobo be here?
一小时内
Within an hour.
为什么晚了
What caused the delay?
有个联调局探员碍事
An FBI agent got in the way.
得确定她不会妨碍行动
I needed to make sure she hadn't compromised our operation.
-她妨碍了吗  -没有
- And has she? - No.
等我的人把她除掉
As soon as my men get rid of her
我会亲自去接马托波  把他带给你
I'll pick up Matobo personally and bring him to you.
你这位朋友
This friend of yours
你确定他有办法
so you're sure he's going to have everything
破解文件吗
he needs to access the files?
他说没问题
He said he didn't think it'd be a problem.
布莱恩  谢谢你
Thank you, Brian.
你对我的帮助及忠诚
For all your help, and your loyalty.
不需要谢我  先生
You don't need to thank me, sir.
我需要
Yes, I do.
经过早上那件事
You're risking a lot to do this
你为我铤而走险
especially after what happened this morning.
等我们拿到U盘上的资料后 再谢我也不迟
You can thank me after we confirm the information is on that drive.
他说钥匙就在垫子下面
Said the key should be under the mat.
找到了
There it is.
你朋友何时到
When will your friend be here?
很快
He should be here any minute.
可以打开空调吗
Would you mind turning on the air?
这里真热
It's really hot in here.
没问题  先生
Of course, sir.
这是萨曼莎和罗杰的合影
It's Samantha and Roger.
这里是萨曼莎的房间  先生
This is Samantha's apartment, sir.
你
You.
我很抱歉  先生
I'm sorry, sir.
为什么
Why?
罗杰调查了他不该知道的事情
Roger was looking into things he shouldn't have.
我想保护他
I tried to protect him too
但被他拒绝了
but he wouldn't let me.
他和你一样固执
He inherited your determination.
是你杀了我儿子
You killed my son.
是你
You...
害死了罗杰
killed Roger.
这是呔哩锭锌  先生
It's Tetradyzine, sir.
一种神经麻醉毒药
It's a neuromuscular paralytic.
别讲话  呔哩锭锌
Don't try to speak.The Tetradyzine
会同时麻痹你的声带
also paralyzes your vocal chords.
如果要说安慰的话  先生
If it's any consolation, sir
罗杰死得没有痛苦
Roger died quickly.
我会尽量
And I'm going to make sure...
让你同他一样
you do too.
情况得到控制
Situation here is in control.
你还在跟踪罗斯小姐吗
Are you tracking Ms. Roth?
是的
Yeah.
该让她回自己的房间了
Time to get her back to her apartment.
你确定这样行得通吗
Are you sure this is going to work?
当然
It'll work fine.
泰勒先生跑去她房间质问罗杰的事
Mr. Taylor came to her apartment to confront her about Roger.
情绪失控后杀了她
Lost his temper, killed her.
然后自杀  怎样
Took his own life, okay?
好的
All right.
如果有问题  我会通知你
I'll let you know if there are any problems.
我真的很抱歉  先生
I really am sorry, sir.
不能让你孤单上路
If only you'd left well enough alone.
-罗斯小姐  -沃斯勒探员
- Ms. Roth.  - Agent Vossler.
亨利·泰勒先生派我过来
Henry Taylor sent me.
泰勒先生在调查
Mr. Taylor's been looking
你说的那件事情
into the matter you discussed.
他认为你现在有危险
He believes you're in imminent danger.
我的天
My God...
我该怎么办
What am I supposed to do?
他希望我
He wants me
把你送到一个地方保护起来
to place you in protective custody.
我送你到藏身处去
Escort you to a safe house.
-现在吗  -我接到的命令是马上带你走
- Now? - My orders are to take you there immediately.
我们可以去一趟你的住所
We can stop at your apartment first
以便你准备些衣物
so you can pack clothes, essentials.
我得给办公室打个电话
Uh, I just need to call my office.
除非我们把你
Not until we get you
送到安全的地方  女士
locked down, ma'am.
请吧
Please.
好吧
Okay.
请这边走
This way, please.
司法部长派来的人还没走
So it looks like your friend from the A.G. is still here.
-我知道  -发生了什么事
- I know.  - What's going on?
他想知道蕾妮在医院里
He wants to talk to me about what Renee did
对坦纳做了什么
to Tanner in the hospital.
蕾妮对坦纳怎么了
What did Renee do to Tanner at the hospital?
我不知道  但哈维尔说她拷问过坦纳
I don't know, but Howell is claiming she tortured Tanner.
蕾妮
Renee?
我不信
I don't believe that.
由不得你不信
Maybe you should.
坦纳一开始什么都不说
Tanner wasn't talking...
然后她把我赶出了房间
and she kicked me out of the room.
接下来他的呼吸机
And then the next thing I know
警报装置被关闭
the alarm on his ventilator is going off.
蕾妮得到情报了吗
And Renee had the information she needed?
如果你当时不在场  你就不会有事
If you weren't in the room, you don't have a problem.
我在场  她让我去牵制他的律师
I do, actually-- she asked me to stall his lawyers.
你去了吗
And you did?
-是的  -你这是怎么了  古德
- Yes.  - Come on, Gold.
你想什么呢
What were you thinking?
她直接命令我  我有什么办法
She gave me a direct order-- what was I supposed to do?
拒绝
Say no.
你知不知道  如果他们证明蕾妮拷问过他
Do you realize if they prove that Renee tortured him
你就成了从犯
you're an accessory?
那时拉里也无法救你
And Larry is not gonna protect you.
我知道  希望一切结束后
I know. Let's just hope the A.G.
司法部长不会再不依不饶
will have moved on to something else when this is all over.
我回去工作了
I'm getting back to work.
莫斯探员
Agent Moss.
有何贵干
What do you want?
抱歉打扰你  不过
Forgive my interruption, but it's just been
我刚听说沃克探员失踪了
brought to my attention that Agent Walker is missing.
不错  她可能已经被绑架
Yes, she may have been abducted
正是那些人
by the same people responsible
绑架了马托波夫妇
for kidnapping Matobo and his wife.
我很遗憾
I'm very sorry to hear that.
我了解你和联调局
And want you to know that I appreciate
正顶着巨大压力
the enormous pressure that you and the Bureau are under.
谢谢
Glad to hear it.
不过司法部长依旧要求
Nevertheless, the Attorney General is still pressing
调查沃克探员对坦纳的
for a full account of Agent Walker's handling
审讯手段  当前形势下
of the Tanner interrogation, and at this moment,
詹尼斯·古德是唯一有空的证人
Janis Gold is the only witness available to me.
她没空  哈维尔
She's not available to you, Howell.
我说过她现在无法抽身
I already told you, she can't be spared right now.
我只需和她说几句话
I only need a short time with her.
不能把她交给你
You can't have her.
别逼我给司法部长打电话
Are you going to force me to get the A.G. on the line?
你不是开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding me.
你非要现在逼我吗
You really want to press this right now?!
我们身陷国际争端之中
We're in the middle of an international crisis.
这我了解
I'm aware of that.
而你关心的只是
And all you seem interested in is
谴责一位生死不明探员的行为
condemning the actions of an agent who's in God-knows-what
然后把她绳之于法
danger just so you can nail her to the wall.
倘若沃克探员有违联邦条例
If Agent Walker broke federal guidelines and used
用非法手段获取情报
illegal tactics to get information,
那么不错  她会受到制裁
then, yes, she will be prosecuted.
那就请你让我们先把她找回来
Then maybe you can let us get her back first
再由你送入虎口
before you throw her to the wolves,
劳您大驾
I mean, if that's okay with you.
什么事
Yes?
拉里  国安局截获一通电话  刚传给我们
Larry? NSA just relayed a call they intercepted to us.
里面提到了蕾妮
Renee was referenced.
提到了什么
Referenced how?
詹尼斯
Janis?
你还是过来亲自听吧
I think you need to come hear it yourself.
我这就去
I'll be right there.
失陪
Excuse me.
我们还没说完
We're not done here.
莫斯探员
Agent Moss!
查到信息源头了吗
Did you source it?
五分钟前
Five minutes ago.
核实无误
It's legit.
再查一次
Check it again.
已经查过两次了
I already did, twice.
拦截代码在哪里
Where's the intercept code?
就在解密算法之上
Right there above the decryption algorithm.
通过优先频道传给了我们
They routed it to us on a priority channel.
是否得到了口头确认
Were we able to get verbal confirmation?
那也无法改变谈话内容  詹尼斯
It's not going to change the content of the call, Janis.
我知道  我只是
I know, I just...
国安局截获了什么录音
What's on the NSA intercept?
你说提到过蕾妮  是什么事
What? You said Renee was referenced. What's on it?
只有一个片段  但提到了她
It's only a fragment, but she's referenced, yeah.
能以此定位对方吗
Enough to get a GPS fix?
片段不到20秒长
The clip's not even 20 seconds long.
只能断定在市内
The best we can say is that it's in the Metro area.
播放
Play it.
爱默生  你说得对
Emerson, you were right,
沃克探员让坦纳招供了
Agent Walker broke Tanner.
坦纳说了多少
How much did Tanner spill?
只有绑架马托波的具体细节
Other than the details of Matobo's abduction, nothing.
你确定吗
You're sure?
沃克无足轻重
Walker is extraneous.
来之前干掉她
Kill her before you get here.
我们很快就到
We'll be with you soon.
动作要快
Be quick about it.
杜巴库急于见到总理
Dubaku's anxious to get his hands on the Prime Minister.
这是何时的电话
When was this call made?
十分钟前
Ten minutes ago.
追查来源
Run a trace.
查过了
I already did.
再查一次
Run it again!
杰克
Jack.
那儿有个坑
The ditch.
干掉她
Kill her.
嗯
Yeah.
托尼
Tony.
下来
Step down.
Step down!
自己走  还是我拽你走
You could either walk or I could drag you.
你真要杀我吗
You're really going to kill me?
我不会求饶
I'm not going to beg for my life, Jack.
你对我说的都是谎言吗
So everything that you told me was a lie?
我也是身不由己
I'm doing what I have to.
我也不期望你能理解我
I don't expect you to understand.
我只知道你是叛徒  刽子手
I understand that you are a traitor and a murderer.
转身
Turn around.
不
No.
我要你看着我开枪
You're going to have to look at me when you pull that trigger.
我让你转身
I said turn around.
信我的话  我保你不死
If you trust me, I will get you through this alive.
跪下
Get on your knees.
我刚才还以为你不会下手
For a second there, I didn't think you were going to do it.
埋了她
Now bury her.
我们时间紧迫
We're on a timetable.
出境之前
Can't have anyone finding the body
不能让别人找到尸体
before we're out of the country.
帮我个忙  托尼
Give him a hand, Tony.